# Full NAME

City · Country · yourEmail@gmail.com · (+212)-666-6666

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A polyvalent Engineer who has 3 years experience as an automotive/embedded/Web engineer and involved in software tests where test cases were developed, automated and executed. Experienced in embedded systems' testing: system test, smoke test, regression test, etc. Efficient in working with geographically distributed teams (Agility: SCRUM).

#### **EDUCATION**

Faculty of Sciences and Technologies

Master degree in Embedded Systems and Telecommunication Engineering

Technical high school

National High School Diploma, Electrical Sciences and Technologies

Settat, Morocco

2013-2019

Fez, Morocco June 2013

#### Work Experience

Capgemini Engineering

\_\_\_\_

Casablanca, Morocco December 2022 – Now

December 2021 – December 2022

Client

Fez, Morocco

Metaneon

Linkedin

Project description

Software Engineer

• Task 1

Project:

- Task 2
- $\bullet$  Task 3

Metaneon Maroc

Self-employed

Project:

Making artistic connected neon signs

- worked on the whole process of the Neon signs creation
- Content creation
- Art Direction
- Automation
- Marketing and B2B and B2C support
- Instagram : Metaneon\_mar

#### SKILLS

- Languages: C, CAPL, Python, REST, ASAM OpenDrive
- Tools: Canoe, vTESTstudio, Matlab\Simulink,IPG Car Maker, ECU-TEST, INCA, TRACE32, DLT viewer
- OSes: Linux (Embedded), Windows
- Protocols: CAN, Ethernet, UDS, XCP, Flexray, LIN
- Documentation: IBM DOORS, RQM, Polarion
- Defect Management: JIRA, IBM RTC Jazz
- Version Control: GIT, SVN
- Standards: ISO-26262, MISRA-C
- Methodologies: A-SPICE v3, AUTOSAR, OOP, V-Model, Agile (SCRUM)

## ACADEMIC PROJECTS

- Safe Drive: Backpack used by Cyclists to prevent them against road accidents
  - Tools: C, Atmel® ATmega328P, PIC16F877A, MPU6050, RF 433MHz, RGB Panel
- Smart Headlight: Automatic control of car headlights
  - Tools: Python, MQTT, Raspberry Pi, Embedded Linux, ESP8266, PiCamera
- Home automation: Prototype of a smart home for devices monitor using a web application
  - Tools: Raspberry Pi, LAMP, HTML, CSS, SQL, PHP, DS18B20, PiCamera

#### CERTIFICATION

- ISTQB certified tester foundation level ID: 81569
- Simulation-Based Testing with Simulink
- Stateflow for Logic Driven System Modeling

## Hobbies

- Camping
- Making visual art with Led Neon
- Music

### LANGUAGE

• English: Full Professional proficiency

French: Bilingual proficiencyArabic: Native proficiency